I want to compliment you in the
я хочу вам сделать комплимент в
modern world when all these you
современном мире когда все вот эти
know women are painted like
знаете женщины раскрашены как куклы
Barbie dolls yes you have this natural
Барби да у вас есть вот эта естественная
feminine beauty it is quite valuable in
женская Красота это довольно ценно в
this
этом
world now it is rare
мире сейчас такое Редко
to meet Well
встретишь Ну
thank you there is such you know energy you
спасибо есть такая знаете энергетика вот
just remind me of my first
аж прям вы мне напоминаете Мою первую
teacher at school you know I remember when
учительницу в школе знаете я помню когда
this little bell opens the door yes
вот это звоночек открывается двери да В
we enter the classroom and she starts like this
класс мы входим и она начинает вот
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Big to you
Большая вам
Heart heart where are you
Сердечко сердечко вы
from at the moment Moscow
откуда на данный момент Московская
region Cool What city is Orekhovo
область Прикольно А какой город орехо
Fominsk Mozhaisk Mozhaisk oh quite an
Фоминск Можайск Можайск о довольно
ancient
древний
city I know I know my father worked in
город знаю знаю у меня отец работал в
Mozhaisk What did he do there and he
Можайске А что он там делал а он в доме
was the
культуры был
manager of the cultural center Cultural center
заведующим Дом культуры
Yes and what did he do there he worked as the
Да и что он тамм делал работал в доме
manager of the cultural center for 3 years and then
культуры заведующим 3 года а потом
moved to Rostov
переехал в Ростов
[music]
[музыка]
Yeah And what is the name
Угу А как вли А как фмили
Serpukhov Serpukhov Yeah Serpukhov is a
Серпухов Серпухов Да ну Серпухов - это
city Well there is a city Well what is
город Ну есть город Ну что фамилия у
his last name ser Am I to blame that at  my last
него сер Я что виноват что у меня такая
name is such a
фамилия такая
last name Well, there was no such thing in a mask
фамилия Ну в маске не было
sir last name
такого сер фамилия
was in the Eighties he was yes no maybe
был в Восьмидесятых годах он был да не
he is not this Maybe he is not the
бы может может он не этим Может он не
manager but just worked
заведующий а просто в этом работал
in this club this is well in the
в клубе это ну в доме
cultural center Well okay and be born I was born in
культуры Ну ладно а родись Я родился в
Rostov already I was born in Rostov it
Ростове уже Я родился в Ростове
turns out He moved uh to here the Institute of
получается Он переехал ээ в тут институт
Culture in Rostov he was invited he
культуры в Ростове его пригласили он
was an assistant teacher
помощник преподавателя был
and then I met my mother they had love there well
и тут маму встретила у них там любовь ну
and I was born And what do you do or did you
и я родился А вы кем работаете или
work as yes no I didn't work I just
работали да нет не работала Я просто
lived in the city periodically I understood Well I'll
периодически жила в городе маже понял Ну
tell you you know Well you are Russian so I'm
я скажу Вы знаете Ну вы русская так я
not I'll tell you So you know yaho you sde
ня я скажу Так вы знаете яхо вам сде
computer
комп
when all these you know women
когда все вот эти знаете женщины
are painted like Barbie dolls yes you have this
раскрашены как куклы Барби да у вас есть
natural feminine Beauty this is
вот эта естественная женская Красота это
quite valuable in this
довольно ценно в этом
world now It's rare
мире сейчас такое Редко
to meet such Well
встретишь Ну
thank you there is such you know energy you just
спасибо есть такая знаете энергетика вот
remind me of my first
аж прям вы мне напоминаете Мою первую
teacher at school you know I remember when we
учительницу в школе знаете я пом когда
open the door yes We enter the classroom and she
открыва двери да В класс мы входим и она
starts this
начинает вот
Big this this
Большая вот это вот это
I have a flashback
прям У меня аж флешбек
and it's funny yeah It's funny yeah she's like that and
так и вот это смех да Смех такой да она
so 4 years
така и так 4 года
Yes thank you for reminding me My
Да спасибо вам что вы мне напомнили Мою
first teacher She
первую учительницу Она хоть и редкостная
was rare but
была но
after after not after her all the girls were
после после не после неё все девушки
beautiful No for me too after the third
красивые Нет у меня тоже после третьего
grade there fourth fifth
класса там четвёртый пятый класс
sixth grade the teachers were so rare
шестой учителя были такие редкостные
[music]
[музыка]
Soviet school Yes it's
Советская школа Да такое
just like that
прям к
unfortunately may he rest in peace
сожалению царство ему
My parents were just
небесное У меня родители просто были
very wealthy and so he was Well
очень обеспеченные вот и он такой
my wife was standing behind these boots
Ну вот моя жена за этими сапогами стояла
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music] It
[музыка]
was like that It was like that
Было такое Было было
I lived in the Soviet Union and
было я При Советском Союзе жила да и у
my parents were very wealthy
меня родители были очень обеспеченные
very carefree
очень об Беспечные
so I wore Italian boots in
поэтому я ходила в итальянских сапогах в
jeans And who were my parents
джинсах А кем родители
what difference did it make were they
были какая разница были были
no
Нет
communists No well where did they come
коммунистами Нет ну
from
откуда
oh dad was a
ой папа был
crane operator high-rise worker his salary was
крановщик высотник у него Зарплата была
when everyone else's The salary was 12,000 he
когда у всех Зарплата была 12000 он
got 1,000 rubles a
получал 1000 руб в
month that's
месяц вот
Ana she would be like
Ана такая бы
that
такая
was And what did she
была А кем она
work And where in trade did she work she
работала А где в торговле работала она
worked in trade and in a pharmacy
она и в торговле работала и в аптеке
work she
работа она везде
worked everywhere In short, she survived as best she could
работала Короче выживала как могла Да
No, we didn't live as best we could we lived well
нет мы жили не как могли хорошо жили у
I remember my
нас я пом
mother ordered a crystal chandelier in Belarus
мама люстру хрустальную в Беларуси
by
заказала по
special order they
спецзаказу
brought such a cultural
привезли культурная такая
chandelier well wash it every 3 months be it
люст ну мыть её каждые 3 месяца быть это
wash It's
мыть Это
just something with
просто что-то с
something no a well-off family was yes And
чем-то нет обеспеченная семья была да А
this crystal chandelier Belarusian
вот эта хрустальная люстра Белорусская
it hung Where in
она висела Где в
Khrushchev Well, in principle, well yes Khrushchevka but
хрущёво Ну в принципе ну да хрущёвка но
for us it was our
у нас это у нас
military how to
военный как это
say it military settlement
сказать военный посёлок
was you understand that is well we had a closed
был понимаете то есть ну у нас закрытый
town it was half
городок был наполовину
closed therefore Yes we had a
закрытый поэтому Да у нас
Khrushchevka well
хрущёвка была ну
three-room apartment well
трёшка
three-room apartment do you regret for the Soviet
ну трёшка была вы жалеете за советским
Union
союзом
m you regret for the Soviet Union I regret
м вы жалеете за советским союзом жалею
Of course my grandfather had an
Конечно у меня у деда вот на в
apartment in Sokolniki in Moscow
квартира
just Sokolniki
просто Сокольников
my grandmother had an apartment on the street
вот у меня у бабушки на улице
Gorky is not there yet there was an apartment we
Горького пока ещ нет была квартира мы
lived there I was brought up there so And what was
там жили я воспитывалась там так А чем
good about the Soviet
чем хорош был Советский
Union what was good about the Soviet Union Yes Oh
Союз чем был хорош Советский Союз Да
you know let's say I could
Ой вы знаете вот я допустим могла
fly to
полететь в
Odessa for the
Одессу на
weekend I could fly to Crimea for the
выходные вот я могла в Крым слетать на
weekend this is You could for the weekend
выходные это Это вы на выходные могли
because your Mom had everything she could
потому что у вас Мама всё что могла
Yes
Да
no I have girlfriends My girlfriends and I didn't
нет у меня подруги Мы с подругами яже не
go alone the fact that my friends were the
одна ездила то что мои друзья были такие
same as me that is
же как и я то есть
[music]
[музыка]
everything
всё
froze aunt I see my neti is starting to
зависло тётку Вижу у меня начинает нети
twitch I
дёргаться
see noka on the flag too Same thing I
вижу нока на ном флаге тоже Тоже самое я
look I talk to beautiful girls about
смотри я с красивыми девушками общаюсь о
love what do you think why Putin attacked
любви как ты считаешь почему Путин напал
Ukraine this is about love
Украину это о любви
no what
нет о
not about
чём не о
love because he wanted it that way and what with
любви потому что он так захотел и что с
whom else are you talking to you No you are
кем ты ещё разговариваешь с вами Нет ты
talking because he wanted it that way And you
говоришь потому что он так захотел А это
answer me you
ты мне отвечаешь
understand I am a woman You are beautiful I
понял Я же женщина Вы красивая
understand why I was so
понял что так раз
nervous oh nercha I had a fight I am
нервничала воо нерча же поругался я
worried with whom I had a fight with my
переживаю с кем поругалась
husband my husband And where is he now at
супругом супругом А он где сейчас
home  and where are you also at home and he is in another
дома а ты где тоже дома а он в другой
room Yes, we have a house on the m floor then Come
комнате Да на м этаже у нас дом то
down Let's make up now I am a
Спустись Давай сейчас мы помиримся Я
family psychologist I can make peace between you
семейный психолог я могу помирить вас
Let's go and First tell me why you
померий Давай пошли а Сначала скажи
quarreled so that I understand the
из-за чего поругались чтобы я понимал
topic Damn, a psychologist is nothing than
тему блин нифига психолог чем всё
telling everything Well, the point is because of cheating because of They
рассказывать Ну суть там из-за измен
just understood Mom why
из-за Там просто понели мама почему
we were married for 19 years we were not cheating so that's
19 лет в браке нас не было изме так то
why and 19 years in marriage Yes, it's already
изза чего а 19 лет в браке Да это уже
hard I understood that because of what Because like because of
тяжело понял то из-за
you
Чего Потому что как бы вот из-за вас
roulettes Because people there say the same thing I why do
рулетки Потому что люди там говорят тоже
you tolerate
я зачем ты терпишь Вот
This humiliation let's
это унижение
go so
пошли так
he said He said yes, I understand
сказал Он сказал да
Why is this why he is wrong why
ясну Почему это почему он не прав почему
your opinion should be respected Let's go Well, let's
надо ваше мнение уважать Давайте пойдём
talk you to
поговори вы к
him you
нему вы
Come up because
Подойдите потому
And you won't come out And say that
что А вы не выйдете А скажите что вот
here the psychologist
тут психолог
asked him not to behave like that because
попросил так не поведёт бо
Lyusha beloved
люша любимый
Ilyusha
Илюша
Ilya
Илья
hears this because you need to be tougher with the
слышит так потому что надо жёстче к
man Ilya come here Ilya will come right away
мужику Илья иди сюда сразу придёт
darling please come down
Илья любимая ну пожалуйста Спустись
here darling my knee hurts
сюда любимая у меня коленка разболелась
not like this won't do my knee hurts I
не так не поведётся коленко разболелось
need to be tough look you're burning Ilya
нужно жёстко Смотри ты горишь Илья
come here and you have to come no don't
Подойди сюда и должен подойти не не
take Okay let's do female manipulation take you have to Look
возьми Ладно давай женскую манипуляцию
take
возьми должен Смотри возьми чашку
some cup or something throw it so it
какую-то или что кинь чтобы она
breaks and and and scream ay run run
разбилась и и и закричи аай бегом бегом
and look We we built this house for 20 years
и посмотри Мы мы этот дом строили 20 лет
each of
каждая
ours you know each glass costs money I
наша знаеш каждый фужер денег стоит я не
can't do that okay take take a
могу такое сделать хорошо возьми возьми
spoon and fork lift it up and fall so it
ложку с вилкой подними и упади чтобы она
rings and and scream oh oh run Yes
зазвенела и и закричи ай ай бегом Да
he'll get scared What happened and
он испугается Что что случилось и
come running to
прибежит на
[music]
[музыка]
help
помощь
or
иль
Ilyusha
Илюша
Ilyusha darling
Илюш любимый ногу
cut her leg or I won't
порезала Илюша или я
leave really
е уйду правда
girlfriends Darling you'll bring it now I'll
подружки Любимый ты сейчас доведёшь я
go to Natasha
уйду к Наташке
[music]
[музыка]
Lyusha drill
люша бурить
herself
сама
ner maybe he just didn't
нер может он просто не
hear then Take a fork on his leg
слышал тогда Возьмите вилку ему на ногу
throw not
киньте не
a dog in ketchup and send to
собаку в кетчупе и отправ к
[music]
[музыка]
a man Well, you are from Ukraine, I am Russia,
мужику Ну вот ты с Украины я Россия
Saint Petersburg, what city Come on, I am the
санкт-петербург город какой Давай я
city of Khmelnitsky Let's try to have
город Хмельницкий Давай попробуем есть
something louder than throw again,
что-то более звонкое чем ещё раз кинь
really throw again
вот реально ещё раз кинь
Ilyusha, please love Come down, I beg you Well,
Илюша люби пожалуйста Спустись тебя
please, well,
Ну пожалуйста ну
PZ Ilya Oh, that's it, in a more commanding tone,
ПЗ Илья О вот так более командным тоном
provocative, men don't like this Ilyusha
вызывающий мужики не любят это Илюша
Ilyusha he needs Ilya either as an order
Илюша ему нужно Илья либо как приказ
or a challenge Ilya Well, please, no, and he will
либо вызов Илья ну пожалуйста нет и он
either obey or come and say What are you
или подчиниться или придёт скажет Ты что
telling me like that Well, he will come, you understand, he will come, we will chat, he will come Ana That's
мне так говоришь Ну придёт понимаешь
not it, he will come Well,
это нет о
he didn't come
придёт Ну вот он не пришёл
So what are we, what else, how to translate the flag of
Так какой мы ещ что как перево флаг
Ukraine, blue and yellow, why is it the sea
Украины голубой и жёлтый почему это море
and sand The thing is that when Stepan
и песок Дело в том что когда Степан
Bandera was Stepan Bandera was on the beach,
Бандера был Степан Бандера был на пляже
he came up with this flag Yes, in Odessa, on the
он придумал этот флаг Да в Одессе на
beach And I didn't know, in fact, I understood this
пляже А я не знала на самом деле эту
story It's
историю
not true, it's true, that at  you still
понял Не правда правда что что у вас ещё
have a ringing
звонкое есть
[music]
[музыка]
you can
можно
get up Dava Dava
подняться Дава Дава
Dava And what will happen if you
Дава И что будет если ты
get up like this Look Our
поднимешься так вот Вот смотри Наша
task is to catch on to communication Yes
задача зацепиться за коммуникацию Да
when there is no communication it is difficult about
когда вот нет коммуникации сложно о
something
чём-то
and a
и
spoon When many of you did not believe how I
ложку Когда вы многие не поверили как я
did it yes father and not much
это сделал да отец анд не много
Hello Hello Zdra Damn how
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Здра Блин как
I [ __ ] waited for you waited somehow waited for the
я бля вас ждала ждала кое как дождалась
sound
звук
you not but seriously now I know in front of you there
вас не а серьёзно сейчас зна перед вами
was a guy like that he knew me the sound I
был тип такой он мне зна звук Я ему
tell him and he told me I realized that he
говорю а он мне я поняла что мне звук
turned off the sound for me there I dont understand anything at all
выключил там вообще не пойму ничего
I Natasha Astrakhan
Я Наташа Астрахань
unexpectedly you were looking for me right for the first
неожиданно вы меня искали пря в первый
time lyric from AST Natasha
раз слы из АСТ Наташа
got to in Russia there are many
попала на в России много
Natashas how do you feel about the war against
Наташ как вы относитесь к войне проти
Ukraine is
укра
it all an old record or something I dont
это всё старая пластинка что ли я не
understand I
пойму Я
love Every day the
люблю Каждый день одно и
same thing bar
тоже планка
flock Well Id better look for another record
стая Ну я лучше в другую пластинку поищу
Okay polo ka what kind of record do you have today
Ладно поло ка какая у ва вас нка сегодня
Well definitely not about the
Ну точно не про
war this is your war not mine Okay
войну это ваша война не моя Хорошо
Lets talk about what are you in the village  you live somewhere
Давайте о чём по вы в селе живёте где-то
in Astrakhan
в Астрахане
Well, almost a village, do you have any
Ну почти посёлок у вас какие-то домашние
pets, I Listen, yes, a dog, chickens, I have
животные есть я Слыш да Собака куры У
a lot of other things,
меня много что ещ
Tavi, there are chickens, and what else, what else do you mean,
Тави цыплята есть А что ещё А что ещ в
everything, ducks, geese, some rabbits,
смыс всё есть утки гуси какие-то кролики
I dont need to
не мне надо
feed them, theyre small, yeah, you can, damn, Im
кормить Маленьки пря да можете блин я
alive and small,
Живые и маленькие
yeah, its dark, theyre already sleeping, damn,
пля Да темно они уж спят блин
show me these PTs, yeah, theyre sleeping, theyre already under the chicken,
Покажите мне этих ПТ Да спят Они уже под
you wont see them anyway, its under the
курицей я ты всё равно их не увидишь это
chicken, show me the chicken,
под курицей курицу мне покажи мне
show me, just yeah, come on, come on, come on, bye, come on, come on, Oh, well,
покажите просто да Ну давай Давайте да
youre on the bunk there, youll see it there, its
Ой ну ты на нара там увидишь там у них
already dark, well, turn on the
уже темно ну Включите
light, wait, I wont turn it on,
свет подожди не включу
Ill be quiet, dont wake up my chicken, you wont see it, its sitting in the shade
я тихо не буди мою курицу ты не увидишь
there, Ill show it to you in the shade, my
она в теньке там сидит Я в теньке покажу
eyes
у меня глаза в темноте
can see it in the dark, over there, its sitting there, smoking, there, there are
видят вон там вон она сидит курится там
no chickens, but theres another chicken somewhere
по не цыплята а другая курица где-то
closer, no, and the others are already there, theyre sleeping,
ближе есть не А другие уже там это спят
Im a cow, you know,  there is such a
я коро корова ты знаешь у меня там такой
[ __ ] there an angry [ __ ] Show me the evil one really
петух злой петуха Покажите злого реально
already came in I will not disturb them
уже зашли я же не буду их тревожить
Why Show me disturb the angry [ __ ]
Зачем Покажите по тревожьте злого петуха
Well this is interesting I have never seen an
Ну это интересно Я никогда не видел
angry [ __ ] really in his
злого петуха реально в его среде
habitat only in cartoons I have seen it
обитания только в мультиках видел му
quietly
тихо
[music]
[музыка]
Show me the [ __ ]
Покажи й петух
[ __ ] there are two [ __ ] there are two
петух там два петуха там два
[ __ ] zti Here is my handsome man Oh my
петуха зти Вот мой красавчик Ой у меня
[ __ ] is really handsome Show me another
петух вообще красавчик Покажите ещё
close-up Show this
крупным планом Покажите этого
[music]
[музыка]
[ __ ] I am not afraid to lift them up they are now right away
петуха Я не боюсь их поднять они сейчас
bring the camera to the [ __ ] this is
разо прямо камеру к петуху поднесите это
real this is a chicken this is not a [ __ ] I have
реально это курица это не петух Я в
seen it in cartoons but it is a chicken [ __ ] here it is a
мультиках видел но это курица петух вот
[ __ ] where is this [ __ ] what are you
он петух да где это петух ты что я тибе
showing you a [ __ ] Can't you tell a chicken from a rooster with a comb
петуха показываю Ты что курицу от петуха
No he doesn't have
отличить не можешь гребня Нет у него
such a comb BC that's
такого гребня нет
enough I understood I looked at that one he wo
ВС хватит понял посмотрел ту
n't get off he won't lay eggs and
слазить не будет яй нести не будет а
why are you going out for years Why are you going out to
зачем вы се лет
show the
выходите показа
[ __ ] Russia has a lot of [ __ ] of
петуха России много пету
beautiful [ __ ] oh very many
ного красивых Петухов ой очень много
very many yes and Where are there more beautiful
очень много да а Где больше красивых
[ __ ] in Astrakhan  or in Moscow or in
петухов в Астрахане или в Москве или в
Moscow I don't
Москве не
know well do you like
знаю ну а вам больше нравятся
Astrakhan roosters or
Астраханские петухи или
Moscow roosters more What are you talking about now well
московские Ты сейчас про что вообще ну
about Roosters a
про Петухов
rooster actually I like everything in Russia
пету вообще-то мне в России все пе тся у
we have the best roosters the best
нас самые лучшие петухи самые лучшие
roosters in Russia yeah Cool yeah Well I was
петухи в России да Прикольно да Ну я
looking once is this rooster a little sick
смотрел как-то он у вас немножко больной
or not are they healthy roosters
этот петух или нет они здоровые петухи у
in Russia or
вас в России или
sick Do you hear now What are you talking about now well do they have
больны Слышишь ты сейчас О чём вообще ну
enough vitamins And you now you
по витаминов хватает И ты сейчас ты мне
now you like translated the topic to
сейчас тему ты сейчас типа смысл перевёл
me you showed him he had some kind of
мне вы ему показали у него какой-то
small comb he told me that he
гребень маленький был мне казал что ему
lacked vitamins He just has a
витаминов не хватает Он просто у меня
Marsh rooster you understand no and
Болотной петух ты понимаешь нет а у вас
in Russia you have a blot tui What do you know
в России блот туи Да ты что ты знаешь
what kind of criminals are cool criminal roosters
какие блатные прикольно блатные петухи
Yes all of Russia is in criminal roosters Yes all of
Да вся Россия в блатных петухах Да вся
Russia is in criminal roosters Yes you know how they
Россия блатных петухах Да знаешь как
peck So wait but it turns out that
клюют Так подожди а получается что
you are running away from them yes Russian Roosters have
бежишь от них да у у российских Петухов
no eggs they don't carry eggs with them they carry them
яиц нет они яйца не носят собой носят с
Well roosters are not  hens carry carry got it
собой Да ну петухи то не несут куры
Russian roosters without e
несут понял российские петухи без е
Russian roosters without e What
российские петухи без е
are you talking about Well, you Yes, they are without eggs
Ты что что ли чи Ну тыж Да они без яйц
or eggs without eggs What are you seriously
или яйца бе яйца Ты что он серьёзно мне
telling me I'm not telling me about Roosters Interesting rooster
гонишь я не мне про Петухов Интере петух
to be eggs that is Russian roosters without eggs
быть яйцами то есть русские петухи без
Russian roosters without eggs Yes of course you
яц русские петухи без яиц Да конечно ты
got it Yes, hens only with eggs got it
что понял да куры только с яйцами понял
Russian roosters without eggs
русские петухи без
Oh I got it about taco What do you
яиц Ой я поняла про тако Ты что
want [laughter] I already caught up already cash you
хочешь Я уже нагнал уже нал ты меня
will see me my rooster when he is next to me I can
моего петуха увидишь когда он рядом мо с
stand with you you got it Like a husband your husband
тобой стоять ты понял Типа мужа ти мужа
I'm telling you seriously your husband rooster
Я тебе серьёзно говорю ваш муж петух
bring him to me come into the flock my rooster will
привед ко мне зайди в стайку мой петух
tear you apart Do you have a personal rooster
порвёт У вас есть личный петух
Russian of course you got it And how is your husband
российский конечно понял А как ваш муж
by the way
кстати
By the way where is he sleeping at home now and what is he sleeping at
Кстати где сейчас дома спит а что он
home They are sleeping here with the roosters They are
дома спит Они с петухами тут спит Они с
here with the roosters because he is sleeping and you are not sleeping with him
петухами тут о потому что спит он а вы
yet And you are not sleeping with him yet
ещ не спите с ним А вы ещё не спите с
but it is important what is so important Well, you  you do
ан важно что так важно Ну тея вы с ним
n't sleep with him because he doesn't sleep with you
не спите потому что он с вами не спит
because
потому что
he or something I can't understand the bliss Understand
он чтоли я се не могу понять негу Поня
you yourself understood you yourself understood what you
ты сам понял ты сам вообще понял что ты
said I didn't understand that he was sleeping and
сказал я не понял что он спит а вы
now you're here in short
сейчас короче тут ле
summer and I was completely shocked I think I was completely
та пролол вообще я в шоке аж думаю
shocked that is he kicked you out of the house howled out of the
пролол то есть онс выгнал из дома выл из
house sko I you Can you show your husband
дома ско я вы А можете показать мужа
maybe show him show your husband if
може показать му он покажите мужа если
he's sleeping really you mean deception
он спит действительно вы значит обману
not I myself can show you but show
не я те сама могу показать а покажите
show at least that he has clothes at
покажите хотя бы что одежда му есть
home I'm sitting in What clothes do you have at home
дома я в же сижу Какая одежда вы к дому
show his clothes that there is a husband there are
покажете его одежду что вот есть муж
his boots coat Everything means there is a
есть его ботинки пальто Всё значит есть
husband Show me the toilet that you have one we don't have a
муж Покажи мне унитаз что он у тебя есть
toilet we don't have a toilet And we have a
у нас нету унитаза у нас нету унита А
toilet I don't understand not the husband or
мым у вас унитаз Я не пойму не мужа либо
he kicked you out and you don't have a toilet I
он вас выгнал га а у вас нет унитаза я
understood everything in short show your husband sweat husband Yes you
поняла всё короче покажите мужа поте
showed your husband your clothes I have
мужа Да одежду те муже свого показывала
roosters Well I can show you a rooster
петухов Ну петуха то я тебе могу
I can show you a dog  show I
показать я тебе могу собаку показать я
can show you everything but I won't
тебе могу всё показать но мужа с не
show my husband everything no need no need my nerves are
покажу всё не надо не надо у меня нервы
n't strong enough to
не такие крепкие чтобы всё
see everything Yes you're all weak
увидеть Да вы все слабые
I'm You're sla Slava You're sitting like this in this
я Вы же сла ты Славы Ты так сидишь в это
not Posh I imagined that you Maybe I'll
не Пош я представил что вы Может мне
show you between the trembling go nah
показать меж дрож пошла
I would have been knocked out if the BC showed
ня меня бы вырубило если ВС показали
me knocked out like your husband
меня вырубило как вашего мужа
nave Oh my
наве Ой
God where is your
Господи где твоя
wife
жена-то
sleeping Show me your
спит Покажи мне свою
wife here Yaha te while
жену вот Яха те пока
I have a rooster Handsome what are you And the chicken
у меня петух Красавчик ты что А курицу
Show me another chicken Show me another chicken Yes
Покажите ещ курицу Покажите ещ курицу Да
I showed you and the dog you said
я тебе показывал а собаку вы говорили
that you can show the dog Show the dog you'll
что собаку можете показать Покажите
be scared honestly And
собаку собаку испугаешься честно А
show me Well I'll try Deja Show the
покажи Ну я постараюсь Дежа Покажите
dog oh
собаку о
big big Show it really Yes he's
большая большая Покажите реально Да он
already sleeping Show him normally he'll
спит уже Покажите нормально гово сей
bark I'll show you how let's do it
залает я тебе покажу его как давайте
normally Let's burn normally show
нормально Давай нормально горим покажите
me the car show the car I already saw but the
мо тачку показать тачку Я и так видел а
dog I didn't see the dog a a a Car
собаку виде собаку не видел а а Тачка
what kind of car do I have come on tell me Well
что что у меня за тачка ну-ка скажи Ну
you're sitting in short  car about dog Zaga
вы сидите короче в тачке о собака Зага
She wants to be shown show show Show
Она хочет чтобы её показали
Now wait I'll
покажите покажите Покажи Сейчас подожди
smoke I'll show yes let's do it why smoke
покурю покажу да давайте так зачем
show dog dog
курить покажи собаку
Let's show dog while you're
соба Давайте покажете собаку пока ты
such a cool guy I'm telling you I'm
такой прикольный парень я тебе говорю Я
cool yes I always get my way
прикольный да Я всегда добиваюсь своего
Show
Покажи
dog Here she wants to be shown vid
соба Вот она хочет чтобы е показали види
she
она
hears sl while this is this is Now the root
слышит сл пока этон этон Сейчас рутка
can take and
может взять и
break
оборвать
SV another will come what's the difference and the other is
СВ другой придёт какая разница а другой
not as cool as Ib
не такой прикольный как яб
Prague another will demand Show me
Прагой другой будет требовать Покажи мне
your toilet
свой унитаз
once one I came across I laughed I blow
один раз один мне попался я во ржала
me a toilet Show showed toilet at
дую мне унитаз Покажи показали унитаз у
Yes do I need what And by the way do you have a wooden one near your
Да надо я что А у Вас кстати у вас возле
garage there is a
гаража есть деревянный тут есть
wooden toilet Yes there is and show me a
деревяный туалет Да есть а покажите
wooden
деревянный
toilet Oh yes just you itself in the entrance
туалет Ой да просто тебя само в подъезде
two are standing wooden this is how And how to
два стоят деревянный это как А как там
sit there is very simple yes Show well
садиться очень просто да Покажите ну
really toilet design have not seen
реально унита конструкцию не видел
wooden
деревянного
Tula Forgot
Туле Забыл
yes
да
for now what to you show dog or toilet
пока тебе что показы собаку или туалет
not I will not go home Come on
не я домой заходить не буду Давай
wooden really interesting how
деревя реально интересно как
Rava  so they called
Рава так назвали
you in Kursk where I live I
ты вообще в Курске где я живу я же тебе
told you Astrakhan region about not
сказал Астраханская область об не
region shch Astra
область ще Астра
Astra I spit Let's show this
Астра плюну Давайте Покажите это
toilet it's really
туалетне реально
interesting the design how high it is
интересно конструк насколько он высокий
how wide how it opens from an
насколько широкий как открывается
engineering point of
инженерной точки
view are you primitive or something
зрения ты первобытный что ли то
just a historian I'm writing a book a historian would be the
просто историк я пишу книгу историк бы
life of the Slavs of the first half of the 20th century ve And
быт славян первой половины XX века ве А
you are not a Slav a Slav too yes a
ты не славян славянин тоже да
Slav Yes and why are you asking me stupid questions What are you
славянин Да а что ты мне глупые вопросы
showing me a toilet
Ты что показываешь мне туалет
showing me a toilet show me a toilet Tua I will not show the toilet They will bring me
показываешь мне
from the war The
Туа унита показывать не буду мне с войны
guys will bring me Then bye Let's toilet Let's
привезут Мне парни привезут Потом пока
toilet normally we
Давайте туалет Давайте туалет нормально
speak books Let's also speak
же говорим
normally but we
кни Давай то же так нормально говорим но
speak you are so strange we are strange we are like a
говорим вы такие чудные мы чудные мы как
snake Show your wooden Tua
змей Покажи свой деревянный
You have never seen a
Туа Ты же не видел
le
ле
Fuh come on come on come on let's go
Фух давай давай давай пошли пошли
[music] let's
[музыка]
go I really have never seen a wooden
пошли я реально не видел деревянного
toilet Shah Shah you are good to him
туалета Шах шах ты ему хороший
you my hoku
ты мою хоку
at all Uncle wants to look at you
вообще Дядя хочет на тебя посмотреть
look at uncle Thank you Hello hello
смотри на дядю Спасибо Привет
You are my
привет Ты мой
sweet Here  my
сладкий Вот мой
toilet Damn it's very far away it's hard to see
туалет Блин очень далеко плохо видно
closer so it's dark outside I
ближе чтоб темно на улице Я же свет
can't turn on the light here I don't have any
здесь не могу включить здесь У меня
light Well then come closer to it Come closer
света нет А ну то ближе к нему Подойдите
Shah Look at your uncle he's here for you Hello I don't
подойди Шах Посмотри на дядю он тебя тут
need your paw Come
Приве не нужна мне твоя лапа Подойдите б
closer Closer to the toilet then he'll be able to
Ближе ближе к туалету он тогда будет
see you better you're my
виднее ты мо
good Here's my
хороши Вот моя
dog no no she's not yapping
собака нене не тявкает
everything And is there a
всё А в туалете есть
light bulb in the toilet no And how do you go to the toilet at night Shut up I'm telling
лампочка нету А как вы ночью в туалет
you And how do you go to the toilet in the dark
Заткнись я тебе говорю А как в темноте
I'm telling you
это в туалет я тебе говорю
shut up shut your mouth you're yelling here at And do you have
заткнись рот закрыл орёшь тут на А у вас
someone fighting in Ukraine would you
кто-то что воюет в Украине бы вы
say that they'll bring you a toilet or are you
говорили что унитаз вам привезут или это
kidding
прикалывались
Well they'll bring it I have a problem with a toilet from Ukraine there's no post to the
Ну привезут Мне с Украины унита поста в
toilet in the World Cup And who is fighting in
туалет в ЧМ пробле А кто у вас воюет в
Ukraine for you I have no one and who will bring it to you
Украине у меня никто а кто же вам
then yes so acquaintances and they went straight for a
тогда да так знакомые а они прям за
toilet
унитазом
and they went for a toilet Let's go for a toilet Let's
поехали а они за унитазом Поехали за
go Yes of course you don't have one, we don't have one
унитазом Поехали Да конечно ты что у нас
toilet they are only
же нет унитаз они же только у
yours no you don't lie down here no need come on
вас не ты не ложись тут не надо давай
without these tenderness sit I don't
без этих нежностей сиди я не
lie down where
ложись куда
I'm afraid I'm really I'm telling you I'll fall and
Я боюсь вот я реально я ве ля я упаду и
[music] I'll
[музыка]
switch off Tell me honestly you
отключусь Скажи честно ты своего мужа
beat up your husband Today
ушатала Сегодня
Senya for bad behavior for bad
Сеня за плохое поведение за плохое
behavior I
поведение
understood And who is stronger to
понял А кто сильнее к
you in charge At seven
ва к вас главный В семь
or
или
together this wouldn't happen It
вдвоём такого не бывает бы
happens Who makes the
бывает Кто принимает решение
final decision together we make But if
окончательно вдвоём принимаем А вот если
you have different views on the
у вас разное зрение на
decision it can be different it can be we quarrel it can be we
решение бывает разные бывает ругаемся
break up But someone makes
бывает расстаемся Но кто-то кому-то идёт
concessions to someone that's all how do you solve this
на уступки вот и всё как вы решаете этот
issue when you well when someone
вопрос когда васпо ну когда кто-то
really doesn't understand For example I don't understand him oh
сильно не понимает Например я его не
when I don't understand him I turn over they
когда я его не понимаю я оборот
get rid of it and everything is cool yes you just need to
избавляют и всё прикольно да просто надо
just understood Do you have children Do you have children
просто понял А дети у вас есть А дети у
joint no
есть совместных нет
And incompatible
А несовместные
incompatible I have how many how many
несовместные у меня есть сколько сколько
days how old are they How old is one 21 the
дй сколько лет им Сколько лет одному 21
second 10 Well yes they are already
второй 10 Ну да это уже
adults Are you afraid that 21 will be taken to
взрослы Боитесь того что 21 заберут на
war No I'm not afraid but  what and
войну Нет не боюсь а что а
what and why should he take it Well Putin
что а почему он должн забрать Ну Путин
will announce mobilization they will take it away and you will have
объявит мобилизацию заберут и будет у
one Well it means that such is fate that is they are
один Ну значит жи судьба такая то есть
simply ready to give you the
просто готовы отдать ти
child will go himself I have nothing to do with it Well it is clear yeah
реб сам пойдёт я ту ни при чём Ну ясно
like 21
да типа 21
years old he will go himself he told me right away
год он сам пойдёт он мне сразу сказал
when it started Well uh here with me he
когда это началась Вот э вот с он у меня
was in the army on conscription he came back from the
был в армии на срочке он мне приехал с
army said he says
армии сказал говорит
mom there will be mobilization I will not go I
мама будет мобилизация я прата не буду я
say I heard you so there was already a
говорю я тебя услышала так уже ж была
mobilization floor Well he was on conscription at
мобилизация пол Ну он был на срочке в
that moment they did not touch him and who do
тот момент его не трогали
you work as you who do you work as a
а вы кем работаете вы кем работаете
seller A What do you sell A What do you sell Oh well
продавец А Что продаёте а Что продаёте
mostly
Ой ну в основном
food mostly I don't like other It's
продукты в основном не люблю другую Это
not mine at the market or in a store
не моя на базаре или магазине
Tell me honestly
магазине Скажите честно
[music]
[музыка]
about the
об
floor it happens that in a store you don't get it I
бы полу бывает чтоб в магазине не обли я
know Well it depends on Who Well it is clear if a
знаю Ну смотря Кого Ну ясно если там
man comes there it is not a sin for him he will
мужичок приходит га его не грех га он
give you everything himself voo And by the way how do
сам тебе всё отдаст воо А вот кстати как
you about Veta weights sign or what
вы об Вете гирки подпи или там какие
weights are there damn now everything is electronic What kind of
гирки блин сейчас всё электронное Какие
rki
рки
know And I don't  I just count the sum, but
зна Причём я не обю просто считаю а
just like the sum, then say plus 5
просто типа сумму Говорите потом плюс 5
rubles, yes, plus
руб Да там плю
10 there, cleverly, yes, chuk-chuk, he bought
10 хитро Да чук-чук налка он купил на
100 rubles worth of cash, and how much do you throw in, somewhere
100 рубли А сколько вы накиды где-то
approximately, well, I'm telling you, it depends on
приблизительно ну я же говорю смотря
who you throw in, well, yes, to whom, how much do you
Кого Кому накидывать Ну да кому сколько
throw in, obligatory, well, it
накиды
happens in different ways, well,
обя ну по-разному бывает Ну вот
tell me, to whom, how it happens, well, with, I'm
Расскажите Кому как быва ну с Я же тебе
telling you, look, to whom, if I'm looking, if he does
говорю смотр кому если я смотрю если он
n't understand at all, I can throw in 100 rubles, to
не соображает могу и 100 руб накинуть
whom, I can throw in 5 rubles,
кому кому-то могу и 5 руб накинуть
cool, yeah, and how much, in short, per day,
Прикольно да И сколько короче в день так
throw in for yourself, it turns
накидайте себе
out, well, I'm playing in different ways, well, per
получается Ну я же игру по-разному Ну в
day, how much are you, 10, it turns out, well,
день сколько там ты 10 получается Ну
plus or minus, yes, what 10, what are you talking about,
плюс-минус да каких 10 Ты
I'm not God, I'm not God, well, how much is
что я же не не Господь Бог Ну а сколько
per day, it turns out, personal
в в день получается
messages are different, well,
личка по-разному Я же тебе говорю Ну да
yes, it happens, and in general, it generally depends
ну бывает и вообще в зависимости вообще
on the people, well, per day, there, with
от народа Ну вот в день там с
traffic, if there's a lot of traffic, then you can
проходимости если большая проходимость
not even
то можно там вообще и зарплату не
get a salary, you can do that in general,
получать Можно так сделать вообще
yes, but if traffic is bad, there are days like
да а ес плохая проходимость бывают дни
that, empty  there
такие пустые там
you
ты
did it and your conscience doesn't bother you then what the hell
сдела а совесть не мучает потом что блин
I basically threw
я короче накинула
you at him yes and you go into church and you go into
ти нему ещ да а в церковь входите а в
church No I'm not a believer that's
церковь входите Нет я не верующий тоже
right that's
правильно тоже
right Well I'm a believer but I'm not
правильно Ну как бы я верующий но я не
baptized and I don't go there I don't even like it's
крещён и туда не хожу мне вообще как бы
not
это это не
my thing And you want church No no I
моё А ты хочешь церковь Нет
think you'll understand me no I just do
нет я думаю ты меня поймёшь не я просто
n't want to because if I come from these
не хочу потому что если я приду из этих
Popes the demon The demons will start
Попов бес Бесы начнут
I do the same I also say the same no I
Я тоже так я тоже так говорю
have a husband in short he's not like there
ня у меня муж короче он ну не то что там
but he's a believer in short it turns out he has
но он верующий у него короче получается
two Faiths because I have him half-breed
две Веры потому что у меня он полукровка
in short His father there is not Russian his mother is Russian
короче Отец там не русский мать русская
he has two Crosses hanging on his neck in
у него на шее Висит два Креста
short and he prays in the morning he prays in the evening I sometimes look
короче и он утром ёт молится вечером
at him and think
молится Я на него порой смотрю думаю
Lord you're a fool you don't understand anything I'm
Господи ты дура ты ничего не понимаешь я
praying for you I say I'm glad that at least
за тебя молюсь Я говорю я рада что хоть
something is for
то-то за
me And look at this other topic you know
меня А смотрите ещё такая тема знаете
why you don't want to If you really come to church
почему не хоте Если вы придёте в церк
I see this Here
это я вижу Вот
you will help him
вы помо
say Well and he is like Yes I
скажет Ну и он такую Да
understood So  I don't believe in God This is my
понял Так что не я в Бога верю Это моя
Faith but the church you don't
Вера но церковь это не
think This is not it yeah well
думаете Это не то
in the church I don't believe in God I believe
да ну в церковь Я не верю в Бога верю а
in the church
в церковь
no I understand But look this I
нет понял А вот смотрите это я так
understand that you bought the car not with your
понимаю что вы машину купили это не на
salary But with the fact that you collapsed and the floor it
зарплату А на то что обвали да полу
turns out no my husband bought it He drives me a taxi and my
получается нет муж купил Он меня таксует
husband too Keith there is a leftist Daki there is a
а а муж тоже Кит там левака Даки там
personal message yeah
личка да
And how can he Well for example there he
А как он может Ну там например ехать он
says the price you understand well the taxi driver
говорит цену ты понимаешь ну таксист он
says the values the person either
говорит ценности человек либо
agrees or not there is no other
соглашается либо нет там другого
option yeah well and he can For example
варианта нет ага ну а он может Например
if he sees some visitors he
если он видит какие-то приезжие он им
tells them three times more expensive they are
там в три раза дороже говорит они же
like
типа
nesha no no no he is an honest
неша не не не не он у меня честный
guy honest and you are honest with him And you are
парень честный а вы с ним честна А вы с
honest with him Yes I understand very well that is you
ним честна Да очень понял то есть вы
won't deceive your own But you can
своих не обману А вот чужих можно
cheat strangers without a bazaar I understand I won't touch my own and
нагреть без базара Поня своих не трону а
strangers at all I understand that is strangers are
чужих вообще Поня то есть чужие
strangers - they are strangers what I
это чужие - это чужие что я же тебе
explained to you I'm looking Who else is on the next day who is
объяснила я смотрю Ещё кого на гряд кого
not people are also different you understand Here
нет люди же тоже разные ты понимаешь Вот
comes a person to you
приходит к тебе человек
oh and so like and when a person
ой и вот как бы и когда тебе человек
comes to you when he comes to you here in
приходит когда вот приходит к тебе вот
general A person comes into the store by
тут вообще В магазин заходит человек по
him you can see him well he went in
нему же видно чувствуешь его он ну зашёл
there bought something why should I
там что-то Купил зачем я буду его
heat it up And some people come in you know these
нагревать А некоторые заходят знаешь эти
useless show-offs you think
понты беспонтовые думаешь
Lord I understand Well yes show-offs are possible and It
Господи понял Ну да понтов это можно а
happened that they piled up some children there some
Бывало такое что детям навали там
five or
какую-то пяти
ten children like not common
десяти детей типа не обший
but from what age already firstly I am a
а с какого возраста уже во-первых Я сама
mother myself firstly secondly my son
мать это во-первых во-вторых у меня сын
when he was
когда
growing up where I live there were neighboring
рос у меня вот где я живу были соседние
stores I just went and said will you
магазины Я прямо ходила и говорил
sell him cigarettes I say I
продадите ему сигареты говорю я вас
will put you in jail they did not sell him cigarettes in my
посажу ему сигареты не продавали в моём
area where I live in another they sold Yes
районе где я живу в другом продавали Да
I
я
know you and I have a very serious
знаю у нас с вами очень серьёзный
discharge I am a representative of the Investigative
разр дава я представитель следственного
Committee of the State Committee your date of birth is
комитета сго комита у вас дата рождения
October 15, 1982 which
15 октября 1982
means your testimony is recorded
года значит ваши показания записаны
testimony is recorded And good then yours
показания записаны А хорошо значит ваши
because it will be a purely heartfelt
из-за того что это будет чисто сердечным
confession
признанием
so it will be possible to do it as a
так можно будет сделать это как
suspended sentence that is, you will not really be put in jail
условное то есть реально в тюрьму вас не
But to responsibility  for
посадят Но к ответственности за
fraud it will still be necessary to
мошенничество всё-таки надо будет чтобы
attract
притянуть
We tomorrow Tomorrow we will conduct investigative
Мы завтра Завтра проведём следственные
actions we will come to the store the store in general
действия приедем в магазин магази вообще
what store will you come to I have not worked for a
в какой магазин ты приедешь Я не работаю
year That's right I have not worked for a year I
год Вот именно я уже не работаю год дома
sit at home look Natalya according to the Criminal Code
сижу смотри Наталь по Уголовному Кодексу
Yes the statute of limitations your statute of limitations for this
Да срок давности срок давности ваш этого
type of crime is 3 years that is everything that
вида преступлений 3 года то есть всё что
you have done over the past years
вы делали на протяжении т последних лет
in the store is
в магазине
subject to
подлежит
consideration Okay come there is a statement a statement
рассмотрению Хорошо приезжайте есть
already you think we
уже вы думаете мы
just have such a job to go to
просто у нас работа такая выйти в
Trust with Show the chicken Show the Tukh
Доверие с Покажите курицу Покажите Туха
we disguise ourselves as
по мы маскируем под
Ukrainians so that you know where I
украинцев для того чтобы ты знаешь где я
live Well tell me my address again look
живу Ну скажи мой адре ещё раз смотри
Natalya here Natalya Liman October 15 in the
Наталья вот Наталья Лиман 15 октября во
year of birth So tomorrow about something is
вго года рождения Так завтра о что-то
already hanging hung immediately
зависает уже зависло сразу
Yes Marik
Да Марик
in a hurry subscribe to y and
вчасне подпишись на й и
I don't know why this is for you to
Я не знаю для чого це то для тоб там
watch on otse face But for you this is about
дивитись на оце фейс Але для тебе це о
two or three clicks But you try me and I
два або три клика Але ти тримае мене и я
will  tell me there are a bunch of fouls and
буду казати в мене там Купа фолов и в
I will be in a great mood for Robbie but
мене буде класний настр щоб Роби но
play the video on y Ista pok Andriy
крути видео пись на й Иста пок Андрий
So let's go with the chick
Так давай ячка